How you doing, officer?
Oh, yes, we will be home every night of the Christmas holiday.
Thank you for your concern.
No, you may not come in.
Do you know that police officer and his gold tooth
asked me why I'm not on the south side?
Ooh, they got a lot of kids over there.
And they garage wide open.
No, I will not mind my business.
That little boy is by himself.
I told you that same van keeps driving up and down the street.
But let me head last junior.
CPS would have been knocking on the door.
Where's your mom and dad?
You hungry?
I'm making chicken sauce.
Do you like chicken sauce?
So you the knee baby, right?
You got a younger brother?
Oh, so all the...
Okay, that's your cousin.
Well, y'all look just alike.
Your family is in Paris?
So the robbers are coming at 9 p.m. tonight
to rob your house.
And instead of calling the police,
you, an eight-year-old,
have rigged the house with explosives and hijinks.
And they ate your pizza?
You need to be an engineer.
We need to get you like an engineering camp or something.
Well, why they so mean to you?
Your mama want to cut up at the airport
and cuss everybody out?
She should have put that same energy
into making sure you were on that shuttle.
Well, I'm glad you knew to go to church.
You got to call him on them.
Baby, he's tearing them robbers up.
Oh, now Kevin Mama want to call and thank me.
Hello?
He's all safe?
Yes.
You're welcome.
Don't let it happen again, okay?
Okay.
I love you.